是什么惊天动地的大消息
So,what's the big news
要我们马上赶过来
we rushed all the way over here for?
我们要宣布的消息就是  公司要我
Our news. My company has asked me
去塔尔萨带领新的分公司
to head up our office in Tulsa.
所以从星期一开始
So as of Monday,
我已经正式被调职了
I'm being officially relocated.
-噢  我的天 -什么星期一
- Oh,my God! - What? Monday?
你要去多久呢
How long do you have to go for?
他们说有可能会长达一年
They said it could be up to a year.
-一年  -那你也要去吗
- A year? - Well,do you have to go?
我似乎是没有选择  不是吗
Well,I kind of have to,don't I?
都是因为这该死的婚戒
Because of this stupid thing.
再也没有比爱妻的支持更棒的东西了
There's nothing like the support of your loving wife,huh?
等一下  你不能去塔尔萨
Wait a minute. Wait,you can't go to Tulsa.
也许你忘了
Maybe you forgot,
但是下星期我们要去看球赛的
but we have tickets to the Jets game next week!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry,
但是我想我可能去不了了
but I don't think I'll be able to make it.
但我们本打算要去看球赛的
But we were gonna go see the Jets!
你不能走
You can't go.
你是维系我们老友圈子的灵魂人物
I mean,you're the glue that holds this group together.
-真的吗  -不是说你
- Really? - Not you.
我真不敢相信你们要搬走了
I can't believe you guys are moving.
-我承接他们的公寓 -不行
- I call their apartment! - No!
-咖啡来了  瑞秋  -谢谢你  乔伊
- Here you go,Rach. - Thank you,Joey.
其实  我不确定
You know what? I'm not even sure
我能不能喝有咖啡因的东西
I can have caffeine.
我和卡罗尔养育本的经验表明
I went through this with Ben and Carol.
一杯咖啡不会影响你的母乳的
One cup of coffee won't affect your milk.
为了安全起见  我要打电话给维纳医生
Just to be sure,I'm gonna call Dr. Wiener.
每次都要淫笑
Every time?
瑞秋  你没必要
Rach, You don't have to
每次有问题都打电话给他  好吗
call him whenever you have a question,okay?
相信我  我是有经验的
Trust me. I know this.
好吧  我相信你
All right. I trust you.
我看到你在拨电话  我不明白为什么
I can see you dialing. I don't understand why..
我在打电话呢  是维纳医生吗
I'm on the phone! Dr. Wiener?
看到罗斯跟瑞秋有了小孩  真是奇怪
It's so weird seeing Ross and Rachel with a baby.
好像大人一样
It's just so grownup.
我知道  是啊
I know,yeah.
觉得好像我们都一起长大了
I feel like we're all growing up.
真有人名字叫"小鸡鸡"  真是笑死我了
A person named "Wiener." God,that kills me
瞧瞧你就像个大人
Look at you all grownup.
事实上  你知道吗
Well,actually,you know what?
我确实长大了
I am,you know?
跟瑞秋之间的事让我意识到
Well,that whole thing with Rachel made me realize..
或许我已经准备好
that maybe I'm ready
接受一段认真的感情了  明白吗
for a more serious relationship,you know?
我想要找一个
Like,I'd like to meet a
善良  成熟  顾家的女孩子
nice,mature,commitment-minded lady.
外表并不是非常重要
And looks aren't as important as..
不  她一定要性感才行
Nah,she's gotta be hot.
我也许认识这样的人
You know,I might know somebody.
要不要你帮我找个对象
How about you set me up with someone,
然后我们搞个四人约会
and we double-date?
可以啊  星期五怎样呢
I can do that. Yeah. How's Friday?
-没问题  -好的
- Done! - All right.
很好  真的吗  好  我们来看看
Good,really? Okay,let's see.
好的
All right.
有个女孩子不错  姗迪·斯黛
You know who's great? Sandy Poopack.
"屎袋"
"Poopack"?
好吧  没关系
Yeah. All right.
那卢娜·"乳头"怀勒也被排除了
Well,that rules out Lana Titwyler.
-我有好消息  -你不用去塔尔萨了吗
- I've got good news. - You got out of the whole Tulsa thing?
好吧  我有个消息
Okay,I have news.
你不用跟我一起搬到塔尔萨
You don't have to move to Tulsa.
你可以待在这里  继续你的工作
You can stay here and keep your job.
太好了  怎么回事
That's great! How?
我跟上司达成一个协议
My boss and I worked out a deal
我一星期在塔尔萨待4天就可以了
where I'm in Tulsa four days a week.
另外3天我可以跟你在一起
So the other three,I can be here with you.
所以你一星期有4天会不在
So you're gonna be gone four days a week?
不行
No.
不好意思  你是习惯性说"不行"吗
I'm sorry,are you just used to saying that?
不是  我不能跟你分开那么久的
No. I can't be away from you for that long.
-真的吗  -是啊  你是我丈夫
- Really? - Yeah,you're my husband.
我不希望
I can not live
一年有208天跟你住在不同州
in a different state than you for 208 days out of the year.
算的真快
That's fast math.
我们塔尔萨分公司需要你
We could use you in Tulsa.
谢谢你试着想出一个不必离别的方法
Thanks for trying to figure out a way,
但是如果你要去塔尔萨  我会跟你去
but if you go to Tulsa,I go with you.
你刚刚竟然没有掩住口鼻做呕吐状
You said that without gagging.
真的耶
I know!
你说什么
Well,excuse me?
是吗  你也去吃屎吧
Oh,yeah? Well,up yours too!
-那到底是谁啊  -维纳医生
- Who the hell was that? - Dr. Wiener.
瑞秋  你不能在凌晨三点打电话给人家的
Rach,you can't call people at 3:00 in the morning.
靠  你说话口气跟他老婆一样
You know what? You sound just like his wife.
艾玛有什么不舒服吗
Was there anything even wrong with Emma?
当然  不然咧  我又不是疯了
Yes,of course there is! Okay? I'm not insane.
是什么问题
What was it?
打嗝
Hiccups.
瑞秋  我告诉过你了
Rachel, I told you,
不能每次有鸡毛蒜皮的小事都打给他
you can't call him every time any little thing comes up.
现在是真的不能了
Well,not anymore I can't.
他不做我们的医生了
He fired us!
我们得另找一个儿科医生了
We have to find a pediatrician.
等一下  莫妮卡说你们小时候
Wait,Monica said that when you guys were growing up..
很喜欢你们的医生
you liked your doctor.
他叫什么名字来着
What was his name?
格曼医生吗
Dr. Gettleman?
不  我认为这不是个好主意
Yeah,no,I don't think that's a good idea.
事实上  他似乎已经去世了
In fact,I think he's dead.
为什么坏事都发生在我身上
Why does everything happen to me?
瑞秋  我保证  明天第一件事
Rach, I promise,first thing tomorrow,
就是找到一个新的医生
we'll find another doctor.
但是我要很早起床
But I gotta get up early,
而且我现在觉得不是很舒服
and I'm not feeling well.
什么  哪里  你不舒服吗
What? Where? You're not feeling well?
你患了什么病  风疹吗
What do you have? Rubella?
别靠近艾玛  她还没有注射疫苗
Because don't go near Emma,she has not had that shot.
仔细想想  倒确实有点像是风疹
You know,come to think of it,it does feel rubella-like.
维纳
Wiener!
维纳  维纳  维纳
Wiener! Wiener! Wiener!
瑞秋
Rachel!
这下好了  现在他知道是我在恶作剧了
Great! Now he's gonna know it was me!
我这身衣服穿去今晚的四人约会如何
So how is this for our big double date tonight?
噢  天啊
Oh,my God.
很好  那正是我期待的反应
Great. Just the reaction I was hoping for.
是啊  你有帮我找个伴吗
Yeah,so you found someone for me?
你没有忘记吧
You didn't forget?
当然没有 你会爱死玛莉·艾伦的
Of course not. And you'll love Mary Ellen.
她真的很聪明  可爱风趣  而且
She's really smart and cute and funny and..
我不能告诉你我是怎么知道的
I can't tell you how I know this,
但是她并不反对3P
but she is not opposed to threesomes.
好吧
All right.
-说说我的约会对象吧 -不行
- So tell me something about my guy. - No.
别这样  透露一点嘛 他叫什么名字
Come on,give me something. What's his name?
麦克
Mike.
麦克  好的  他姓什么呢
Mike. Okay,what's his last name?
该死  就不能为浪漫保留点神秘感吗
Damn it! Is there no mystery left in romance anymore?!
那好吧
All right.
几小时后与你和麦克在餐厅见
We'll see you and Mike at the restaurant in a couple hours.
好的  没问题  待会见  拜拜
All right,great. See you. Bye-bye.
我为什么要说麦克呢
Why'd I have to say Mike?
我根本不认识叫麦克的
I don't know a Mike!
我怎么就没说个别的什么名字
Why couldn't I have said..?
里面根本就没有男生的号码
There's no guys in there!
要找个好医生真是难
It's impossible to find a good doctor.
要如何分辨哪个是好医生
How do you know the good ones..
哪个又会拿阴茎摩擦你的膝盖呢
from the ones who'll push their penis against your knee?
什么
Excuse me?
我知道她的意思
I know what she's talking about.
我们要找个新的儿科医生
Well,we've gotta find a new pediatrician.
罗斯昨晚不舒服
Ross was getting sick last night,
艾玛或许也被感染到了
and Emma may have caught it.
你为什么不去找格曼医生呢
Why don't you see Dr. Gettleman?
罗斯说他去世了
Ross said he died.
他才没去世
He didn't die.
我上星期才遇到他女儿
I just saw his daughter last week.
她说他很好
She said he was fine.
但是她本人  可被肉毒杆菌搞惨了
Her,on the other hand,botched Botox.
太好了  那我要带艾玛去找他
Great. Well then,I'm gonna take Emma to see him.
为什么罗斯说他死了呢
I wonder why Ross said that he died?
或许他把他
Maybe he was getting him confused
跟他小时候的心理医生搞混了
with his childhood therapist.
他看过心理医生
He saw a therapist?
他以前常常做重复的噩梦
He used to have a recurring nightmare.
吓死他了
It freaked him out.
哇  什么噩梦呢
Wow,what was it?
梦到我要吃掉他
That I was going to eat him.
麦克
Mike!
怎样
Yeah?
好吧
Okay.
真不敢相信  我竟然跟你做这事儿
I can't believe I'm doing this with you.
我才刚结束一段九年的恋情
Although I did just end a nine-year relationship..
所以我应该敞开胸怀  迎接一些挑战
so I should be open to taking some risks.
一切都会没事的  好吗
Everything is gonna be fine, ok?
按照我的指示就行
Follow my lead.
你只要假装是麦克就可以了
All you have to do is pretend to be Mike.
-我就是麦克啊 -演的真不错
- I am Mike. - Attaboy.
她们来了
Here they come.
我是菲比
I'm Phoebe.
嗨  菲比  我是麦克
Hi. Phoebe. Mike.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
乔伊  这位是玛莉·艾伦·詹金斯
Joey,this is Mary Ellen Jenkins.
麦克  你跟乔伊是怎么认识的呢
So,Mike,how do you and Joey know each other,anyway?
我跟乔伊是怎么认识的呢
How do Joey and I know each other?
太多人问这个问题
If I had a nickel for every time
如果每次给个硬币  我都成富翁了
somebody's asked me that.
-在学校认识的 -我们在大学认识的
- From school. - We met in college.
我是说高中
I mean high school.
那你们认识可久了
You guys go way back,then.
那你现在是做什么的呢
So,what are you up to these days?
-我是律师 -麦克  大律师噢
- Well,I'm a lawyer. - Mike,attorney at law!
-事实上  我才刚放弃执照  -什么
- Actually,I just gave up my practice. - What?
这种事你应该先跟我说一下的
That's the kind of thing you usually run by me.
我一直想成为专业钢琴家
I always want to play piano professionally.
如果现在不赶快做  就来不及了
If I don't do this now,I never will.
太好了  我喜欢音乐家胜过律师
Great. I like that better than the lawyer thing.
正因此我才一直等到现在
Which is why I waited until now
才介绍麦克给你
to introduce you to Mike.
你不是还以为他是律师吗
You thought he was still a lawyer.
不  我并没有那样说
No,that's not what I meant.
我们帮你点杯鸡尾酒吧
Let's get you a cocktail.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
帮你在塔尔萨找个在餐厅的工作
Looking for restaurant jobs for you in Tulsa.
真是贴心  有找到吗
That's so sweet. Did you find anything?
-"鲜有收获"  -没找到  是吧
- Slim Pickins. - Nothing,huh?
不  "鲜有收获"  是间烤肉店
No. Slim Pickins. It's a barbecue joint.
他们在找厨师
They're looking for a cook.
事实上  说厨师有点夸张
Actually,"cook" may be a bit of a stretch.
他们在找人去铲豆子
They're looking for somebody to shovel mesquite.
"鲜有收获"  听起来真不入流
"Slim Pickins"? That is so cheesy.
"不入流"餐厅也在招人
Well,So Cheesy also has an opening.
亲爱的  没关系
Honey,that's okay.
我认识一个叫南茜的人
I know this woman,Nancy..
她是专门帮餐厅招人的
who's a restaurant biz headhunter.
她或许会知道一些职缺
She may know something.
我真是太感激你愿意跟我去
Can I say how much I appreciate you coming with me?
等我们抵达塔尔萨
When we get to Tulsa,
我会带你去"鲜有收获"吃大餐的
I am taking you for a great dinner at Slim Pickins.
那"不入流"呢
So Cheesy?
全猪餐厅呢
Whole Hog?
在塔尔萨要保持犹太饮食洁净的习惯真难
It's gonna be tough to keep kosher in Tulsa.
嗨  南茜吗
Hi,Nancy?
嗨  我是莫妮卡·盖勒
Hi,it's Monica Geller.
我很好  我需要在塔尔萨找份工作
I'm good. Listen,I'm looking for a job in Tulsa.
是啊  我丈夫被调职到那边
Yeah,well,my husband's been relocated.
因为我爱他
Because I love him.
不  我不想要在纽约的工作
No,I don't want a job in New York.
杰屋在招人吗  我的天啊
Javu's looking? Oh,my God!
他点名要我  噢  我的天啊
He asked for me personally? Oh,my God!
哇  我真的是太受宠若惊了
Wow,this is really,really flattering.
但是我要搬到塔尔萨了
But I'm moving to Tulsa.
所以  请你告诉杰屋
So,just,if you would tell Javu..
我接受这份工作
I'll take it!
我是瑞秋·格林
My name's Rachel Greene.
我有帮艾玛预约看诊
I have an appointment for Emma.
格曼医生快看完病人了
Dr. Gettleman is finishing up with a patient.
-他等下就会出来  -好的  谢谢
- He'll be out shortly. -OK, thank you.
我想你只是感冒了
I think you just have a cold.
绝对不是感染了链球菌
It's definitely not strep.
谢了  医生
Thanks,doctor.
要不要来根棒棒糖呢
Would you like a lollipop?
那还用问吗
Do you even have to ask?
他还活着
He is alive!
真的好奇怪
It's so surprising that
你跟乔伊认识那么久了
you and Joey have known each other for so long..
而我却从没有听说过你
and I've never heard about you.
因为我们之前闹翻了
That's because we had a bit of a falling out.
麦克开车撞到我妈
Mike hit my mom with a car.
不  我没有
No,I didn't.
没关系  我已经原谅你了
That's okay. I have forgiven you.
现在我们又是朋友了  一切都很美好
Now we're friends again,and everything's great.
等一下  你妈还好吧
Well,wait. Is your mom okay?
别插嘴  我们在聊天呢
Please,we're trying to have a conversation.
你在《我们的日子》中亲切多了
You're a lot nicer on Days of Our Lives.
《我们的日子》
Days of Our Lives!
怪不得你看起来那么眼熟
That's why you look so familiar!
-什么 -什么
- What? - What?
什么
What?
你们彼此不认识吗
Do you not know each other?
我们当然认识
Of course we do.
他是在玩我们高中常玩的游戏
He's playing a game we used to play in high school.
我们假装不认识
We pretend we don't know each other.
我们玩很多种游戏的
We played all kinds of games.
你还记得有一次
You remember that one
你因为太蠢而被我揍吗
where I punch you in the face for not being cool?
让我问你一个问题
Let me ask you something:
乔伊有几个姐妹呢
How many sisters does Joey have?
-6个 -不  他有7个
- Six. - No,he doesn't. He has seven.
你搞什么  我出了7个指头
What are you doing? I said seven!
乔伊  为什么你要介绍陌生人给我呢
Joey,why did you set me up with a stranger?
因为我忘记了约会的事
Because I forgot about our date.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
另外要澄清一下 我没有开车撞他妈
And just to be clear,I didn't hit his mother with a car.
你简直不可理喻
You are unbelievable.
我花了那么多时间帮你找
I spent so much time finding
完美的对象  你知道吗
the perfect girl for you, you know?
玛莉·艾伦又聪明又可爱  又很随便
Mary Ellen is really smart and cute and loose.
嘿
Hey
你别装了吧
Who are you kidding?
你在街上随便找个男的塞给我
You find some guy off the street for me?
天啊  真是太侮辱人了
God,this is humiliating!
菲比  我很抱歉
Phoebe, I'm so sorry.
如果你不喜欢这一个
If you don't like this guy,
我可以帮你找个更好的
I can find you a better one.
麦克  麦克
Mike? Mike?
我要走了
I'm out of here.
很高兴认识你
It was nice meeting you.
你也要走
You're leaving too?
你要是能说出我的名字  我就留下
I'll stay if you can tell me my name.
晚安
Have a good night.
亲爱的  我们明天就要走了
Honey, we are leaving tomorrow,
而你还有好多东西要打包
and you still have a lot of packing to do.
你说得对
You're right.
或许我不应该去
Maybe I shouldn't go.
什么
What?
南茜告诉我
So Nancy told me about
有一个很棒的餐厅在招人   杰屋
this job at this great restaurant,Javu?
离塔尔萨不太远
But it's just a little outside of Tulsa.
那是多远呢
Well,how far outside?
在曼哈顿
Manhattan?
你要接受那份工作吗
And you're thinking of taking it?
你之前说跟我在一起
So, before,you said that being with me
比任何工作都重要
was more important than any job.
但我猜  现在的重要性顺序是
But I guess now it's
旧工作<我<新工作
old job,me,new job.
我会想念这只手的
I'm gonna miss this hand!
我知道这很过份
I know this is a lot to ask..
但是  天啊  钱德勒
but,my God, Chandler,
现在是千载难逢的好机会
this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
你之前不是说你无法忍受
What happened to "you can't live without me
一周有4天不能跟我在一起吗
four days a week"?
如果你仔细想想
Well,if you really think about it,
其实  4天并不是很长的时间
I mean,four days is not that long.
星期一你去上班前我会见到你
I mean, I see you Monday before you go to work..
然后星期四晚上我也会见到你
and Thursday when you get back..
而我总是在星期二忙到很晚
and I always work late on Tuesdays,
所以如果你仔细想想
so really if you think about it..
事实上只有分开一天而已
it's really just one day.
而如果我们连一天都撑不住
And well,if we can't make it one day,
我们真的是有大问题了  朋友
we got real problems,my friend.
我认为你应该接受这份工作
I think you should take the job.
真的吗
Really?
是啊  当你像猴子一样鬼吼时
Yeah. I know it must be important to you
我就知道这对你一定很重要
when you start chattering like a monkey.
真是我听过的最甜蜜的话
That's the nicest thing anybody's ever said to me.
新医生怎么样
How was the pediatrician?
我真的很喜欢他
I really liked him.
是啊  是啊  真的  真的
Yeah,yeah. It was really,really,
真的很不错
really good.
-你答应我不会说出去的 -我知道
- You promised not to say anything. - I know.
罗斯仍在看他的儿科医生
Ross still sees his pediatrician!
我不在乎
I don't care.
真的假的  你还在看格曼医生
Are you serious? You still see Dr. Gettleman?
他是医术高明的诊断师
He is a brilliant diagnostician!
是诊断师还是哄小孩大师呢
Diagnostician or boo-boo fixer?
罗斯  说真的
Ross, Seriously,
你该去看合适的医生
you gotta go to an appropriate doctor.
为什么  我知道是有点怪
Why? Why? I know it's a little weird,
但是他是个很棒的医生  好吗
but he is a great doctor,okay?
他知道我的病史
He knows my medical history.
而且每次我去看病
And every time I go in there,
他都非常慎重其事
he makes a big deal.
他会说"瞧  我最喜欢的病人来了"
You know,"Look,it's my favorite patient."
他是不是说完之后
Does he say that before
就把体温计插到你的肛门里呢
he sticks his thermometer in your tushy?
我可记得某人
I seem to remember someone
把他的安全感毛毯带到大学宿舍
bringing his security blanket to college.
那不是安全感毛毯  那是壁毯
That was not a security blanket. That was a wall hanging.
可它大多数时间都不是挂在墙上的
It didn't spend much time on the wall!
不好意思
Excuse me.
嗨  我一直希望可以再遇到你
Hi. I was hoping to run into you.
我们可以谈谈吗
Can we talk?
当然
Sure.
我真的很抱歉  我觉得太丢脸了
Look,I'm sorry,really. I'm so embarrassed.
拜托
Please.
真的  我是个还不错的人
Really,I'm a pretty nice guy.
你可以问我的保释官
Just ask my parole officer.
显然  我说的笑话不好笑
Apparently,I'm not a funny guy.
你那天为什么同意那样做呢
Well,why did you go along with that?
因为他告诉我
Because I was told that
我可以吃一顿免费的晚餐
I'd get a free dinner,
不过最后仍然付钱了
which I didn't.
而且他说我可以认识漂亮的女生
And that I'd meet a pretty girl,
那倒是真的
which I did.
确实如此
That's true.
那你告诉我的事有哪些是真的呢
Well,is anything you told me about yourself true?
我名字真的是麦克
My name is Mike.
而且我真的会弹钢琴
And I do play piano.
证明给我看
Prove it.
这里并没有钢琴
There isn't a piano here.
对真正的钢琴家来说  不算是问题吧
That wouldn't stand in the way of a true pianist.
好吧
Okay.
你真的很棒
You are really good.
我会弹一点吉他
I play a little guitar myself.
是吗  那太好了
Really? That's great.
你弹奏什么音乐呢
What kind of music do you play?
像是原声乐  民乐之类的
Like acoustic,folksy stuff,you know?
但是我现在在制作
But right now I'm working on
铁娘子乐队的CD封面
a couple lron Maiden covers.
你觉得  或许  有空的话  我可以
Do you think that,maybe,sometime,I could..
没关系的  来吧  约我吧
It's okay. Go ahead,ask me out.
好吧  如果有空的话
Okay. You think,maybe,sometime
我可以约你出去吗
I could take you out?
你真是让我一点心理准备都没有
You just caught me off guard.
好啊  我很乐意
Yeah,that would be nice.
瞧瞧  我最要好的两个朋友
Look at this! My two best friends!
不好意思  我也不想为难别人
Excuse me. I don't mean to be a jerk..
但是那个长疹子的婴儿
but the baby with the rash
是在我后面进来的
came in after me.
医生等一下就可以看你了  先生
The doctor will be right with you,sir.
妈咪  我找不到华多
Mommy,I can't find Waldo.
马戏团吗  他在大象后面
What,the circus? He's behind the elephant.
哇  你的孩子一定也很迷华多吧
Wow. So your child's a big fan of the Waldo books too?
是啊  所以我也很熟
Yeah,that's how I know.
-对了  我叫罗斯 -嗨  我叫莎莉
- I'm Ross,by the way. - Hi,I'm Sally.
你没带婚戒
So no ring.
所以我推想你也是单亲家长
Can I assume you're also a single parent?
我的确是单亲父亲
I am a single parent.
很艰难  不是吗
It's hard,isn't it?
根本没有社交的时间
There's no time for a social life.
要去哪里认识朋友呢
Where are you gonna meet someone?
其实  或许
Let's say,I don't know,
可以在儿科医生那里认识人吧
you met someone in the pediatrician's office.
小罗斯  轮到你了
Rossie? We're ready for you.
是啊
Yeah..
走吧  小罗斯  轮到我们了
Come on,Ross Jr. It's time to go in.
妈咪
Mommy.
妈咪  那个人是怎么了
Mommy,what's wrong with that man?
嘿  是我帮你找到华多的耶
Hey,I helped you find Waldo!
-太好了  你还没走 -你去哪了
- Good,you haven't left yet. - Where have you been?
有事情在格曼医生那耽搁了一下
I got held up at Dr. Gettleman's office.
有一个家伙  把别人都吓到了
There was some guy that freaked everybody out.
你正好赶上
You got here just in time.
我马上就走了  兄弟
I really have to go,buddy.
噢  兄弟
Oh,man.
亲爱的  答应我一下飞机就打电话
Honey. Promise to call me when you land?
当然  我爱你
Of course I will call you. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
不要舌吻  二位  儿童不宜
Watch the tongue,people. We got a baby over here.
-再见  钱德勒  -再见
- Bye,Chandler. - Bye.
-再见  亲爱的 -再见
- Bye,honey. - Bye.
-怎么了  乔  -我很生气你要走
- What's the matter,Joe? - I'm mad at you for leaving.
你什么都不会  就会抛弃人家
You know,you're nothing but a big leaver.
带着笨行李的负心汉
A big leaver with a stupid suitcase.
你是不是故意想挑架
Any chance you're trying to pick a fight
让离别不那么伤感呢
to make all of this easier?
老兄  你真是太了解我了
Dude,you see right through me!
好了  那再见了  莫妮
Okay,well.. Bye,Mon.
再见  罗斯  瑞秋
Bye,Ross. Rachel.
-再见  艾玛 -好了  拜拜
- Bye,Emma. - Okay,bye-bye.
旅途愉快  好了  噢  天啊
Have a good trip. Okay. Oh,my God.
钱德勒  等一下
Chandler, Wait.
重要性排名是旧工作
It goes old job..
新工作
new job..
最高的是你
and you.
我必须向你说清楚
This is just something I have to do.
我知道
I know.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
我也知道
I know that too.
别担心  我很快就会回来的
Don't worry. I'll be back before you know it.
是的  一切都不会变
Yes,it will be the same.
因为我就是知道
Because I know,that's how.
我保证
I promise.
你可以双重保证吗
You double promise?
一下飞机就打电话给我
Call me when you land.
-轮到我说了吗 -好的  再见
- Can I talk now? - Okay,bye.
-乔伊 -他要登机了
- Joey! - He had to board.